awakeningfromalzheimers.com 2019-06-14

# Awakening from Alzheimer’s Privacy Policy – Awakening From Alzheimers

The website you are visiting is owned and operated by Online Publishing & Marketing, LLC. Online Publishing & Marketing, LLC owns the brands Cancer Defeated, Natural Health Insiders, Awakening From Alzheimer’s, Aging Defeated, and the Alternative Cancer Research Institute. We understand your concerns regarding collection of your personal data. We appreciate your trust and respect your privacy. To find out more about how we use data to learn about how people interact with our website, you can email us at [info@awakeningfromalzheimers.com](mailto:info@awakeningfromalzheimers.com).

Except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell or disclose information that identifies you personally or makes it possible for other parties to contact them directly without your consent.

**Security:**  We use the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an advanced security protocol that protects your credit card information and ensures secure online ordering. SSL Internet connections are encrypted, and thus protect all credit card ordering information, including your name, address and credit card number, so it cannot be read in transit. We use secure technology, privacy protection controls, and restrictions on employee access, to safeguard your personal information.

**Collection of Information:**  We only collect personally identifiable information about you via this website when you provide it in connection with a request for a product, service, or information. For example, if you decide to place an order, we will ask you for your shipping and billing address, phone number, email address, credit card number and its expiration date. When you enter your personally identifiable information on this website, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you would prefer that we not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any such information.

We may also collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of this website, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular.

This website is intended for adults. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. However, if the parent or guardian of a child under 13 believes that the child has provided us with personally identifiable information, the parent or guardian of that child should contact us at [info@awakeningfromalzheimers.com](mailto:info@awakeningfromalzheimers.com) if they want this information deleted from our files so that it is not in retrievable form. If we otherwise obtain knowledge that we have personally identifiable information about a child under 13 in retrievable form in our files, we will delete that information from our existing files so that it is not retrievable.

**Use of Cookies:**  We also use cookies to assign identification to your computer. The unique user ID contained within your cookie automatically identifies your computer to our servers every time you visit our website. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user, but may be correlated with identity information in our log files. You can turn off the cookie feature by using your browser preference options.

**Third Parties:**  We may rely on other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include data analysis firms, customer support specialists, web hosting companies, and fulfillment companies (e.g., companies that fill product orders or coordinate mailings). We may share personally identifiable information with such third parties as appropriate for them to perform their functions. We may also share personally identifiable information with marketing partners or other direct marketers, so they can send you notices about products or services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive marketing communications from them, see the Opt-Out section below.

Our website may offer links to and from other third party sites. These third parties have separate data collection and privacy practices independent from ours, and thus we cannot be responsible for their policies or activities. Please contact those third parties directly if you have questions about their privacy policies.

**Email Marketing:**  We want to communicate with you via email correspondence only if you want to hear from us. We may from time to time send you email messages describing new products, special offers, and great values. If for any reason you would no longer like to receive email messages please see the Opt-Out section below.

**Opt-Out:**  You may opt-out of receiving communication from us and from other third parties by emailing us at: [info@awakeningfromalzheimers.com](mailto:info@awakeningfromalzheimers.com) or writing to us at:

**Online Publishing & Marketing, LLC**  
**PO Box 1076**  
**Lexington, VA 24450**

In addition, when we contact you via email, we will include instructions to unsubscribe from future emails if you so choose.

Please note, if you decide opt-out, you may still receive transactional email messages regarding your order (i.e. order confirmation, shipping information, customer service notifications, etc.).

**Legal Requirement:**  We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform with the law, respond to claims or comply with legal process served on our company or the website; (b) protect and defend our rights or property, the website, our employees, guests or the public.

**Merger/Sale:**  In the event  **Online Publishing & Marketing, LLC**  
and/or any of our assets are acquired by an unrelated third party, as the owner of this customer information, we may disclose or sell the information as an asset of the company in conjunction with the sale of our company or the sale of a portion of our assets to a third party. While we will endeavor to require the successor company to maintain this privacy policy, we cannot guarantee that our policy will remain in effect.

**Notification of Changes:**  We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy.

**Rest assured, your privacy is protected. We DO NOT sell your email or any**  
**personal information to third parties. You can unsubscribe any time you wish.**
